addmyarticles.com 2011-12-31

# article directory submission,articles directory submission,article directories submission,articles directories submission

## Privacy Policy

**Addmyarticles.comCustomer Internet Privacy Statement**

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Addmyarticles.com collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site.

This policy applies only to the Addmyarticles.com website and not to other websites to which Addmyarticles.com is linked.

**Collection of information**

Users of the Addmyarticles.com website may be asked for information when attempting to join to submit articles or when requesting an article be sent to them via email. It is necessary to retain registration information for all users who submit articles to the Addmyarticles.com website, so that every author using our service may have their own account.

We do not retain the email addresses of users requesting an article be sent to them via email.

**Sharing and Use of information**

Information that we request for the purposes of registration is not shared with anyone outside of the owners and staff of **Addmyarticles**.com.

Information that we request for the purposes of registration is not used for advertising, promotional or informational purposes at this time, however we reserve the right to send email to a registered user's email address(es) to inform said user(s) of updates or changes to our service or terms or other important information regarding their submissions or account with **Addmyarticles**.com .

Under no circumstances will Addmyarticles.com sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

Any information contained within a submitted article will be publicly visible to anyone. If you intend to keep your personal information to yourself, please do not include information about yourself in any submitted article.

**Use of Cookies**

The Addmyarticles.com website does not use or set cookies on a users computer. This statement may not reflect the practices of advertising partners Addmyarticles.com chooses to partner with. 

**Security**

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**Changes to this policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy in the future. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be published on this page.  

Registration and use of this website is accepted as an acknowledgement and agreement of our posted [Terms & Conditions](http://www.addmyarticles.com/termsconditions.php) and [Privacy Policy](http://www.addmyarticles.com/privacy.php). Users who find our [Terms & Conditions](http://www.addmyarticles.com/termsconditions.php) and/or [Privacy Policy](http://www.addmyarticles.com/privacy.php) disagreeable are not allowed to use the Addmyarticles.com website.
